WHAT'S UP SO FAR?
TURING NOLAN, LET'S GO
TO A DIFFERENT RIDE.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY
RAN OUT OF ROOM,
THOUGH. YEAH, YOU GOT
TO GO.
MY NAME'S TURING. WHAT'S
YOUR NAME?
ELLEN. ELLEN, NICE TO
MEET YOU. OH, THIS
IS TERRIFYING. HEY, TURING,
DON'T BE AFRAID.
SURELY THIS ISN'T SCARY,
RIGHT?
BUT KIDDING TO WATCH
TURING BE TERRIFIED WASN'T
ALL I HAD IN
STORE. EVERYTHING IN THIS
STORE BEHIND YOU IS
FREE ON ME.
GO AHEAD, COME ON.
I GOT A FLY.
THIS IS LIKE A
FREE CANDY STORE WITH
FREE CANDY. EVERYTHING YOU
GRAB IS FREE. SO
THAT'S FREE, FREE, FREE.
THEY'RE EXPENSIVE AND THAT'S
WHY IT'S AWESOME. BECAUSE
IT'S ALL FOR JIMMY'S
CREDIT CARD. YEAH, THAT'S
GONNA MAKE IT EVEN
BETTER.
HERE, YOU WANT A
PURSE? IT'S YOURS. YOU
WANT WHATEVER THIS IS?
IT'S YOURS. YOU THINK
THIS IS AS HIGH
AS YOU CAN GO?
OH, BUDDY.
I COULD GO HIGHER.
THE KIDS WERE FILLING
UP THEIR CARD SO
MUCH. SHE IS JAM
-PACKING IT. I DECIDED
TO BRING IN SOME
FRIENDS TO HELP THEM.
SO WHAT'S BUDGET? I'LL
LIMIT IT. THE WHOLE
STORE IS FREE.
INFINITE BUDGET. YOU GUYS
WANT TO HELP SANTIAGO
GRAB A BUNCH OF
STUFF? HE'S BARELY WORKED
OUT SO I'M MAKING
HIM WORK OUT. OH,
BARELY WORKED. OKAY, YEAH.
THIS IS ALL FOR
SANTIAGO RIGHT HERE. YEAH,
LET'S OPEN UP ONE
FOR SANTIAGO. YEAH, THIS
IS SANTIAGO RIGHT HERE.
OH, THIS IS SANTIAGO.
THAT'S SANTIAGO.
SANTIAGO, THAT'S WHOLE STORE.
LOOK HOW HAPPY THEY
ARE. THIS HAS BEEN
AN AMAZING EXPERIENCE. LET'S
GO. HELP MORE PEOPLE.
IT WAS LOVELY MEETING
YOU. THANK YOU.
AND IN CASE YOU'RE
CURIOUS,
IF A KID DOESN'T
WANT TO BE IN
THE VIDEO, THEY DON'T
HAVE TO BE IN
THE VIDEO AND WE
STILL GRANT THEIR WISH.
LIKE, THIS KID RIGHT
HERE DIDN'T WANT TO
BE IN THE VIDEO.
THAT'S PERFECTLY FINE. THE
VIEWERS AT HOME, HOW
COULD THEY HELP SUPPORT
SOMEONE THEY MIGHT KNOW
THAT HAS CANCER? VOLUNTEER
AT THE LOCAL HOSPITAL.
GOING TO READ THE
KIDS IN THE HOSPITAL.
OR HONESTLY, IF YOU
HAVEN'T VISITED ONE OF
YOUR FRIENDS OR SOMEONE
YOU KNOW THAT HAS
CANCER IN HOSPITAL, JUST
GO VISIT THEM. I'M
SURE THAT WOULD MEAN
THE WORLD TO THEM.
I HEARD SOME OF
YOU GUYS WATCH OUR
VIDEOS. SO I WANT
TO SAY HI. IT'S
GOT A MONITOR, A
BRAND NEW IPAD POWER
PC.
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO
PLAY WHATEVER COMPUTER GAMES
YOU WANT. TAKE CARE,
MAN. GLAD I GOT
TO MEET YOU. THANK
YOU. NO WORRIES.
OR NEXT WISH. WE'RE
HEADING TO THE STEELERS
FACILITY, JUST SURPRISE JEREMIAH.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
SOON ENOUGH, BECAUSE WE'RE
JUST GETTING STARTED.
JEREMIAH'S DREAM IS ABOUT
TO COME TRUE.
TO PLAY FOR THE
STEELERS IS SOMETHING HE'S
ALWAYS WANTED TO DO.
GENTLEMEN, ARE YOU READY?
READY?
NOBODY'S COMING.
GO DEEP.
GO, JERRY. GO, JERRY.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAPPY?
YEAH.